one of the primary refactorings in
的主要重构之一
IntelliJ IDEA is called the extract
IntelliJ IDEA被称为摘录
method refactoring the way this works is
重构工作方式的方法是
you first select a block of code that
您首先选择一个代码块
you'd like to extract into a new method
您想提取一种新方法
and that block will become the method
那个方块将成为方法
body any inbound variables into the
将所有入站变量放入
block will be added as parameters to
块将作为参数添加到
your new method in order to activate it
您的新方法以激活它
I can simply press ctrl alt M and choose
我只需按ctrl alt M并选择
the destination class where I'd like
我想要的目的地班
that method to be inserted here since
该方法要插入到这里
it's inside an anonymous inner class
它在一个匿名内部类中
I'll choose to put it in the outermost
我会选择放在最外面
class here that's the messenger now I
我现在在这里是信使
can give this method a name set its
可以给这个方法命名
visibility and return type which is
可见性和返回类型是
automatically set for us based on the
根据我们自动为我们设置
code we've selected and then declare
我们选择的代码，然后声明
it's static if I don't want it attached
如果我不想附加它是静态的
as an instance method you'll notice that
作为实例方法，您会注意到
this will add a new parameter for the
这将为
field that we're using inside this block
我们在此块内使用的字段
since it won't be visible inside the
因为它在
static method I can also choose to fold
静态方法我也可以选择折叠
the parameters as well and here what
参数以及这里的内容
fold means is to collapse two or more
折叠意味着折叠两个或更多
parameters into a nested method call
将参数放入嵌套的方法调用中
outside of the extracted method so now
现在所提取的方法之外
let's apply this refactoring and see
让我们应用此重构，看看
what happens so you can see where the
会发生什么，以便您可以看到
method is invoke that instead of passing
方法是调用而不是传递
node and message in a separate
节点和消息在单独的位置
parameters we've collapsed them into a
参数，我们将它们折叠成一个
nested method called and then passed
嵌套方法调用然后传递
that return type into our new send and
将返回类型输入到我们的新发送中，
log result method which accepts a
日志结果方法接受
pending result and returns a void now
待处理结果，现在返回空
let's demonstrate that same refactoring
让我们演示一下相同的重构
without the parameter folding enabled
没有启用参数折叠
now we accept two parameters fire the
现在我们接受两个参数
message log the result and return
消息记录结果并返回
avoid extract method also has the
避免提取方法也有
ability to detect duplicate blocks and
检测重复块的能力以及
replace them with the new method
用新方法替换它们
invocation
调用
so here I'll extract this statement into
所以在这里我将这个陈述解压缩到
a new method called debug will declare
一个称为debug的新方法将声明
it static and then apply the refactoring
它是静态的，然后应用重构
so extract method will detect those
因此提取方法将检测到那些
locations and replace them with a call
位置并将其替换为通话
to the new method here there are three
到这里的新方法有三个
and let's step through them one by one
让我们一步一脚印
now you can see that in addition to
现在您除了可以看到
statement that I've refactored three
声明我重构了三个
others were detected and replaced as
其他被检测到并替换为
well with the new method invocation
新方法调用很好